Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/thongnguyen-82b62a15a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Blender Zeplin Web Design

Thong Nguyen

Product Designer

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Hi, I'm Thong, designer specialized in creating beautiful, yet functional websites or digital interfaces. I love helping clients to achieve their goals and grow their business. I'm a very passionate designer who always eagers to learn, grow and try something new.

Experience

DiA DEMY

UX/UI Teacher

June 2022 - Present (2 years 10 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

VNPAY

Product Designer

June 2021 - Present (3 years 10 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Freelance

UI/UX Designer

November 2020 - June 2022 (1 year 8 months)

Orient Commercial Joint Stock Bank (OCB)

Graphic Designer

May 2019 - October 2020 (1 year 6 months)

vincom

Handling graphic design tasks as assigned

Participating brainstorming sessions to finalize artworks for marketing and usage campaigns(events, promotions...)

Designing artworks as well as collaborating with other designers in the projects

FE CREDIT

Product Manager Credit Card August 2018 - April 2019 (9 months) Sacombank

2 years 4 months

Senior Product Development Specialist June 2015 - June 2016 (1 year 1 month)

Partnerships Executive
March 2014 - June 2015 (1 year 4 months)

Citi

Universal Banker May 2013 - February 2014 (10 months)

Hochiminh city

Education

DPI Graphic Design Training Applications
Graphic Design · (2019 - 2021)

Stenden

Master's degree, International Hospitality & Service Management · (2016 - 2017)

University of Derby

Master's degree, International Hospitality & Service

Management · (2016 - 2017)

Victoria University of Wellington

Bachelor of Commerce and Administration, International Business and Marketing \cdot (2008 - 2012)